forumco.com 2017-12-10

# ForumCo Privacy Statement

**ForumCo Privacy Policy**

ForumCo has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: ForumCo.com. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user occassional information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings. We **do not** sell user information to any third party.

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at any time. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

You can send email to info@forumco.com 

We use Google AdSense on our website, you may view their privacy statement here,

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. The privacy of our visitors to forumco.com is important to us. 

At forumco.com we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit forumco.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 

We also use third party advertisements on forumco.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

**DoubleClick DART cookies**  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx 

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact,

Padraic Lavin

ForumCo Support  
info@forumco.com
